Το Plex ζήτησε 120€ για να συνεχίσετε να βλέπετε από τις συσκευές σας.
Το πλήρωσα εγώ το ποσό.
Αν χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά και μπορείτε,
οποιαδήποτε συμβολή θα εκτιμηθεί.
Hey, Sein!
That mage said they'd take our photo.
A photo? What's that?
Don't worry about it. Come on.
This is the start of our legend!
Like a fairy tale
It's a sign the story has reached its end
Like a single passage taken from
A journey that was too long
Of the evil that once cast a shadow
Across this land
And the memories of the short journey
With the hero who defeated it
The story ends
And the hero goes to sleep
Leaving this land with
Days of peace and quiet
The passage of time heartlessly
Makes people forget
Even the tracks left behind by his life
Begin to rust
Just the same
Your words and wishes and courage
Are still inside of me
And they live on
We chose the same path
That's all it was supposed to be
Why is it that at some point
I wanted to understand the reason for
The tears that fall down my cheeks
Even now
If I retrace the journey we walked together
Even though you're not there
I know I'll be able to find it
Is he really a strong warrior?
He's a dwarf who's protected the village
we're heading to for almost 400 years.
What's the life expectancy of dwarves?
About 300 years.
His name is Old Man Voll.
He's a long-lived friend of mine.
I want to chat with him before he dies.
That's not funny.
But it's true that there aren't many people
who can talk about the past with you.
Perhaps a detour like this one
isn't so bad once in a while.
Maybe I'll stay for a decade or so.
We're staying one week at most.
That's the village?
Old Man Voll.
It's been a while.
Well? Doesn't he seem cool,
like an old, seasoned warrior?
He's way beyond old.
Remind me. Who are you?
He's totally decrepit.
It's me, Frieren.
Ah, yes.
You're still pretending to be senile?
Huh?
Most deaths in battle
are due to carelessness.
It's the greatest weakness
of both demons and people.
Can't stand, can you?
Even the most experienced warriors
can easily suffer fatal injuries
if they're not attempting
to defend themselves.
If I'd drawn my sword then,
you'd be short one leg.
Your strategies are as underhanded as ever.
Frieren.
You are welcome here. Make yourself at home.
Wait, Frieren.
I can't walk.
Stark, train with him while you're here.
Okay.
He's one heck of an old man.
You're welcome to use this firewood.
I'd like to stay here for a decade.
Find us some work.
Ms. Frieren, we're only
staying up to one week.
Okay, fine.
It's a small village.
No one else would take the job,
so I appreciate it.
It's not like we have anything else to do.
Anyway, I had no idea
Old Man Voll had friends.
I've never seen him converse
so happily before.
He's a senile old man.
Normally he struggles
to hold a conversation.
He's protected the village from monsters and
demons for years, but nobody knows why.
He's like our protective deity.
He's been alone this whole time.
A week flies by, doesn't it?
How is Stark?
Humans develop quickly.
He's improved a fair bit.
I see.
I had fun, Old Man Voll.
I'm really grateful to you now.
You're the reason I got to know
Himmel and the others.
Old Man Voll, why do you
defend this village?
It's ancient history now.
It doesn't matter.
People don't risk their lives
for things that don't matter.
I'm just defending the village my wife loved.
She was a human.
I'm merely keeping the promise
I made a long time ago.
But I won't say more on the subject.
I couldn't adequately describe
her face, or voice, or eyes.
This is my memory alone.
It's silly, isn't it?
I've been keeping a promise
I made to a dead woman.
You're right.
But I'm sure she's glad
you're keeping your promise.
Himmel, you're a good hero.
I'm sure you'll defeat the Demon King.
My wife wished to see the era of peace that
comes after the defeat of the Demon King.
I'll carry the memory of the great
hero Himmel into the future.
I appreciate it, but you
don't have to do that.
I have Frieren and Eisen in my party.
I won't live as long as an elf.
Then it'll be Frieren's job.
She'll carry our memory into the future.
Right?
Fine, I guess.
I see.
You've been blessed with good companions.
Later, I'll have to show you
the collection of handsome poses
I came up with.
Actually, maybe I won't remember you.
I probably didn't need that collection
of handsome poses after all.
I wasted my memory.
Do you remember that hero's face?
Of course I do.
And his voice?
Don't insult me.
I remember everything.
Himmel is the reason I decided
I'd get to know people.
Like your reason for defending this village,
it's important to me.
I see. A reason, huh?
I can't remember anymore.
Not her face, nor her voice, nor her eyes.
But I continue defending this village
for an important something.
You're quite the jokester, Old Man Voll.
By the way, where are you headed?
We're heading to Aureole,
the land where souls rest.
Where is that?
Ende, where the Demon King's castle is.
I see.
So you're finally off
to defeat the Demon King.
I hope that brings peace to the land.
Old Man Voll, the Demon King is...
What is it?
I'll carry your memory into the future, too.
I wouldn't mind that.
I'm glad I got to see you
at the end of my life.
You said the same thing eighty years ago.
Goodbye, Old Man Voll. Take care.
Frieren.
I dreamed of my wife.
I see.
Maybe it's because you and I
reminisced about the past.
See you later.
Were you asking him something?
I'm looking for someone.
You remember why I'm on
this journey, don't you?
Isn't it to travel with a sexy older woman?
That's important, too.
But this is the goal of my journey.
To reunite with my friend
who departed ten years ago.
Oh, right.
A photo? You don't see those often.
It was taken by a mage who visited
my village a long time ago.
Have you figured out where he went?
We've been traveling along major
roads in the northern lands.
Along the way, we've met
people who have seen him.
We can probably keep heading north.
That was ten years ago, right?
I'm surprised anyone remembers seeing him.
He has a unique name.
It leaves a strong impression.
What's his name?
Gorilla Warrior.
Yeah, okay.
So what's his real name?
His real name?
Are you sure you guys were best friends?
Everyone in the village always
called him Gorilla Warrior.
Actually, he made them call him that.
How does that even happen?
By the way, I'm Goatee Priest.
No one asked.
Did people call you that even
before you could grow a goatee?
Are we still talking about this?
Either way, it's good enough if they
recognize the name Gorilla Warrior.
He'd definitely be calling himself that.
Sounds like a weird guy.
Yeah. He's a weird guy.
Once we cross this canyon
and walk for about a week,
we'll finally be in the
magical city of Äußerst.
This really has been a long journey.
What are you looking at me for?
I didn't do anything wrong this time.
Can we stop by a village first?
The road branches here.
Sure. We'd like to rest, too.
Ten years ago, did someone who called
himself "Gorilla" come this way?
That's a wild question.
Ah, you must mean Mr. Gorilla Warrior.
Wow, he knows who that is.
I remember him, since he
left a strong impression.
He defeated a monster that
appeared near the village.
Do you know which way he headed after that?
I'm not sure...
Oh!
Mr. Gorilla seemed close with the stubborn
old woman who lives on the plateau.
You should ask her.
"Stubborn old woman"?
That's quite the nickname.
I'm a stubborn old woman, you see.
I'm not telling you for free.
She even calls herself stubborn.
What should we do?
You'll perform several tasks for me.
First, deliver this letter to Nagel,
a blacksmith in the neighboring town.
It's just a simple errand.
It reminds me of my journey with Himmel.
You did things like this?
Helping people by running errands
was a daily occurrence.
And it always turned into troublesome
searches or monster hunts.
Don't jinx us.
In any case, let's do what we can
to get her to open up to us.
This old woman just refuses to open up.
They don't call her stubborn for nothing.
Sorry. Himmel or Heiter could've
gotten her to open up in half a day.
But our party only has
socially awkward members.
This is the last one.
Polish the heroes' statue in the canyon.
Come with me. I'll show you the way.
What heroes' statue?
It's a stone statue of the heroes said
to have saved the world a long time ago.
That's all I know.
They're forgotten heroes.
No one even knows their names.
The village has been looking
after it for generations.
Forgotten heroes, huh?
By the way, you're Goatee Priest,
aren't you?
How'd you know?
We're here.
A priest and a warrior.
It's pretty old.
They kind of look like Mr. Sein
and Mr. Gorilla.
I think I recognize the warrior.
It's Kraft.
You're right.
It looks just like him.
Shall we get started?
Sein?
I see.
So this person's name is Kraft.
What about this one?
I don't know.
I see.
What's this statue?
Don't they look just like us?
According to the chief,
they're ancient heroes.
But nobody even remembers their names.
We won't end up like that.
I refuse to be forgotten.
I'm going to become
an unforgettable hero like Himmel.
Even the greatest heroes
are forgotten someday.
Even Himmel, who defeated the
Demon King, will be no exception.
I guess you're right. It's impossible.
You think I could get this big
if I worked out hard enough?
Gorilla Warrior.
From now on, that's my name.
Why?
If I want to become an unforgettable hero,
then I need a memorable name.
You're right.
Then your name is Goatee Priest.
That's a great name.
I'm sure a goatee would look good on you.
We're finally done.
That was a lot of work.
We could've used magic if it
were a bronze statue.
I asked Gorilla to polish it, too,
but he didn't do as good a job.
His only strength is fighting.
But his name sure was memorable.
Gorilla talked about you a lot.
He said the two of you would become heroes
whose names would be remembered forever.
Did you figure out where Gorilla went?
Tür.
It's a trading city in the middle
of the northern lands.
That's a long ways east from here.
It's in the opposite
direction from Äußerst.
Yeah.
What am I going to do?
And you alright
Can you hear me
Trailing along deserted train tracks
Crying excessively
Wanting you to smile
I hold on to memories I'd like to keep fresh
There's something I'd like to tell you
With words more precious than a goodbye
Unremarkable yet special
See, things that couldn't have been
Seen if it weren't for these eyes
Why? They begin to overflow
So, if I were to be born again
I would surely choose this place once more
So, if we were to meet again
I'd never let you go, I'd choose the present
Even if no promises were made
Even if I'm lost in days of loneliness
Those tears will be alright,
dawn will surely break
I'm whispering our lullaby
for you to come back home
Join me in the other room, one at a time.
Make yourselves at home.
Yeah, it's all my fault.
Because mediating is a priest's job.
The medicine is ready.
You're embarrassing me.
I'm pretty handsome when
I'm being considerate, aren't I?
I guess it's not so bad.
Take care, then.